Guide to the Profiles of Stanford Faculty and Staff
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Profiles of Stanford faculty and staff
1979-1986
SC0739
Stokes, Donald.
1 Linear feet 69 audiocassettes
Collection includes audiocassettes, some typescript drafts and partial transcripts of tapes, press releases, and copies of the finished article published in the CAMPUS REPORT.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Alternative Formats
The audiocassettes have been digitized and are available in streaming format.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Stokes joined the Stanford University News Service as an academic writer in 1978; prior to that he had served as British consul-information in San Francisco (1962-78). He was known as Stanford's Boswell for the hundreds of news profiles he wrote on faculty and staff. He received his bachelor's degree at the University of London in 1941 and served with the Royal Navy and the British Foreign Service before moving to San Francisco in 1960. He died in 1986.
Description of the Collection
Collection includes audiocassettes, some typescript drafts and partial transcripts of tapes, press releases, and copies of the finished article published in the CAMPUS REPORT.
Access Terms
Stokes, Donald.; Interviews.; Oral histories.; Stanford University--Faculty.; Universities and colleges--Faculty.
Collection Contents
- Campus Report Articles
  - Bacon, Harold and Rosamond, 1985; 2.1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bandura, Albert, 1985; 2.2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bernfield, Audrey, 1985; 2.3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bower, Gordon, 1985; 2.4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Boxer, Steve, 1985; 2.5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brown, Judith, 1985; 2.6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Carlson, Don, 1985; 2.7-2.8 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Castle, Terry, 1985; 2.9 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cole, Sally, 1985; 2.10 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Craig, Gordon, undated; 2.11 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Di Piero, Simone, 1985; 2.12 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dupre, John, 1985; 2.13 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Flanagan, Robert J., 1985; 2.14 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Frank, Joseph, 1985; 2.15 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Fredrickson, George, 1985; 2.16 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Gagnier, Regenia, 1985; 2.17 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Goheen, John, 1985; 2.18 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Greenberg, Joseph, 1985; 2.19 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Hampshire, Sir Stuart, 1985; 2.20 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Howell, James E., 1985; 2.21 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Huestis, Wray, 1985; 2.22 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Juillard, Alphonse, 1985; 2.23 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Knudsen, Eric and Phyllis, 1985; 2.24 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Leiderman, Herbert, 1985; 2.25 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Lindenberger, Herbert, 1985; 2.26 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Macheim, Kurt, 1985; 2.27 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Noddings, Nel, 1985; 2.28 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Noll, Roger, 1985; 2.29 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Patrick, Cynthia, 1985; 2.30 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Perry, John, 1985; 2.31 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Raleigh, Ed, 1985; 2.32 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Rees, John, 1985; 2.33 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Salgo, Sandor, 1985; 2.34 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Sinclair, Loraine, 1985; 2.35 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Staiger, Robert, 2.36 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Stone, Bill, 1985; 2.37 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Thompson, Richard, 1985; 2.38 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Thoresen, Carl, 1985; 2.39-2.40 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Wandell, Brian, 1985; 2.41 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - White, Robert, 1985; 2.42 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Wiggins, Lyna, 1985; 3.1 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Wine, Jeffrey and Marlene and Nina, 1985; 3.2 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Wright, Gordon, 1985; 3.3 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Wu, Yuan-Li, 1985; 3.4 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Wynter, Sylvia, 1985; 3.5 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Audio recordings
  - Bacon, Harold and Bacon, Rosamond, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Bandura, Albert, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Bernfield, Audrey, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Bower, Gordon, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Boxer, Steve, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Judith, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Carlson, Don, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Castle, Terry, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Cole, Sally, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Craig, Gordon, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Di Piero, Simone, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Dupre, John, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Flanagan, Robert J., 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Frank, Joseph, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Fredrickson, George, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Gagnier, Regenia, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Goheen, John, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Greenberg, Joseph, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Hampshire, Sir Stuart, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Howell, James E., 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Huestis, Wray, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Juillard, Alphonse, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Knudsen, Eric and Phyllis, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Leiderman, Herbert, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Lindenberger, Herbert, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Macheim, Kurt, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Noddings, Nel, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Noll, Roger, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Patrick, Cynthia, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Perry, John, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Raleigh, Ed, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Rees, John, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Salgo, Sandor, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Sinclair, Loraine, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Staiger, Robert, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Stone, Bill, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Thompson, Richard, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Thoresen, Carl, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Wandell, Brian, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - White, Robert, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Wiggins, Lyna, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Wright, Gordon, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Wu, Yuan-Li, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Wynter, Sylvia, 1985; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Wine, Jeffrey and Wine, Marlene, 1985; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Bailey, Thomas, 1977 Jul 20; 5.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - [Vandagriff, Robert?], 5.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Arthur, Bryan, 5.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Tom, 5.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Adams, Rod, 5.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Dowley, Edith, 5.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - [Barton, Ed?], 5.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - [Bacon?], 5.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - George, Alex, 5.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Nanney, Herb, 5.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - [Illegible], 5.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Dallin, Alexander, 5.12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - McConnell, Harden, 5.13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Mexico [Clark W. Reynolds], 5.14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Knoles, George, 5.15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Walker, Henry A., 5.16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - [Bradwin?], John, 5.17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Franklin, Marc, 5.18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - [Illegible], 5.19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - [Illegible], 5.20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - [Illegible], 5.21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
- Transcripts, Press Releases, Clippings (Box 4)